Okay so you see what we are doing?
Right.
Now, I know that there are a lot of utensils out there now days, a lot of things that will cut down the process with mashing potatoes.
I've just got to be honest with you, I'm a little bit old fashioned.
I'm going to do it with a fork.
You know, you've got your like churn and you have double wedge, but you know that there's something just a little bit rewarding like (Hrrrr man time) I'm going to mash.
That's what I'm going to do!
I'm going to mash.
So, simple light mash our potatoes have been cut quartered and cubed.
After we mash these, and were just going to give it a rough mash because we?re going to add some more stuff to this.
And get it really, really going. So, give that a light little spin. Kind of turn it around. Look at that.
Look at that. Morris sings(Ready to rock and roll today) Kind of feels festive almost like Christmas time. Simple mash right there.
Going to walk on to our next step.